

CONTACT ME

<u>miguelseguramx@gmail.com</u>

in @miguelseguramx

@miguelseguramx

+52 55 5964 3832

<u>miguelseguramx.com</u>

EDUCATION

Anthropology FCPyS / UNAM 2019 - 2020

FrontEnd Architecture
Platzi

Platzi 2019

JavaScript Career

Platzi 2019

Programming Fundamentals

Platzi 2019

English B1 - C1 CELEX / IPN 2016 - 2018

LANGUAGES

English - C1

Spanish - Native

MIGUEL ANGEL SEGURA VAZQUEZ

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm a Full Stack Developer with 3 years of experience who loves to get involve in creative and challenging projects with the best practices like: Clean Code, Test Driven Programming and an excelent Git flow.

I love to learn new things and be very agile. I also take the initiative to resolve my problems and take the situations to the next level.

Likewise, I think that I reflect a lot in my work the values and what I have learned as a Hiker, Dancer, and Bodybuilder.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

<u>LeonidasEsteban.com</u> | September 2020 - Present

In <u>LeondiasEsteban.com</u> I worked with a small team that allowed me to be in contact with all areas of the business, always trying to improve to achieve our goals,

Here I Own, Design and Code projects from start to finish. Involving on all the process of Software Development, from the DB and API Design to take care of the pixel perfect Frontend Implementation using React.

I really enjoyed mentoring other developers through code reviews and pair programming sessions.

Worked with:

- React.js
- Django
- Python
- PostgreSQL
- Redux
- Three.js
- Node.jsDjango
- AWS
- Djaligo
- Docker
- TDD

React Developer

KIUX | May 2020 - September 2020

As a React software developer, my responsibilities were migrating a law firm's internal web applications from jQuery and Vanilla JS to React.js and create new features like a small dashboard with the most important metrics of every worker

Worked with:

- React.js
- JavaScript
- jQuery